{"id": "v_001", "subject": "participant_a", "act": "V", "modifier": "none", "utterance_type": "express_other", "target": "participant_b"}
{"id": "nv_001", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "none", "high_level_action": "search", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "available"}
{"id": "nv_002", "subject": "participant_a", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "pointing at", "high_level_action": "draw attention", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "leaflet"}
{"id": "nv_003", "subject": "participant_a", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "none", "high_level_action": "verify", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "participant_b"}
{"id": "nv_004", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "pick up", "high_level_action": "select", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "3039_bright-red 1, 3001_bright-red 1, 3004_bright-red 1"}
{"id": "v_002", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "V", "modifier": "none", "utterance_type": "agree", "target": "participant_a"}
{"id": "v_003", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "V", "modifier": "none", "utterance_type": "declare_selection", "target": "participant_a"}
{"id": "nv_005", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "drop", "high_level_action": "discard", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "3001_bright-red 1, 3004_bright-red 1"}
{"id": "nv_006", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "hold", "high_level_action": "inspect/check", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "partial model 1"}
{"id": "nv_007", "subject": "participant_a", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "flip", "high_level_action": "search", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "leaflet"}
{"id": "v_004", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "V", "modifier": "none", "utterance_type": "instruct", "target": "participant_a"}
{"id": "nv_008", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "pick up", "high_level_action": "select", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "D_blue 1"}
{"id": "nv_009", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "hold", "high_level_action": "inspect/check", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "D_blue 1"}
{"id": "nv_010", "subject": "participant_a", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "pick up", "high_level_action": "select", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "D_red 1"}
{"id": "nv_011", "subject": "participant_a", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "hold", "high_level_action": "inspect/check", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "D_red 1"}
{"id": "nv_012", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "NV", "modifier": "attempt to", "low_level_action": "none", "high_level_action": "assemble", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "D_blue 1"}
{"id": "nv_013", "subject": "participant_b", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "none", "high_level_action": "search", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "available"}
{"id": "nv_014", "subject": "participant_a", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "place", "high_level_action": "discard", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "D_red 1"}
{"id": "nv_015", "subject": "participant_a", "act": "NV", "modifier": "none", "low_level_action": "none", "high_level_action": "inspect/check", "utterance_type": "none", "target": "leaflet"}